Franz Boas Papers 1862-1942 Mss.B.B61.inventory9 Mss.B.B61.inventory09
American Philosophical Society
- Franz Boas Papers - Correspondents M
  - Meyer, Willy (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Jan. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 July 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 May 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1904 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1905 Sept. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 13
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Feb. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Jan. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 July 10; 1p.
  - Meyerhoffer, Marie (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1921 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - (Enc: Copy of letter from Marie Meyerhoffer to G. E. Stechert & Co.), dated Oct. 21, 1921
    - Marie Meyerhoffer -- to G.E. Stechert & co., 1921 Oct. 26; 2p.
  - Meyers, Reuben (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1904 Dec. 5; 1p.
  - Meylan, George L. (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1908 May 12
    - To Boas, 1905 Mar. 27
    - To Boas, 1908 May 13
  - Meyrowitz, E. B. (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1908 May 25
    - From Boas, 1908 June 6
    - To Boas, 1908 May 23
  - Mezhdunarodnaya, Kniga (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1930; 1p.
  - Michael, Arthur (Box 63)
    - Arthur Michael -- from B. Laufer, 1905 Jan. 25
  - Michael, Jerome (Box 63)
    - See Pegram, G. B. to Cabanellas, 1937 Feb. 11
  - Michael, Ray (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1934 June 8; 1p.
  - Michael, W. H. (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1904 Nov. 23; 1p.
  - Michaelson, Ida (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Mar. 3; 1p.
  - Michel, Arthur (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1936 Mar. 9; 2p.
      (Enc: Michel, Artur. Der Spanische Volkstanz. 7p.)
  - Michel, Frederich (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1906 Feb. 19; 2p.
  - Michel, Max F. (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1940 May 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 May 8; 1p.
  - Michelitsch, Anton (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1922 Nov. 11; 1p.
  - Michelson, A[lbert] A[braham] (?) (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1910 June 2
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 18
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 17
    - To Boas, 1910 May 31
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 20
    - To Boas, 1921 Apr. 7; 1p.
  - Michelson, D. Julius (Box 63)
    - 1934 Jan. 24
  - Michelson, Nicholas (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 16; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Feb. 24; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Apr. 23; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1939 May 3; 2p
    - To Boas, 1939 July 18; 2p
    - To Boas, 1940 Oct. 20; 1p
    - To Boas, 1940 June 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec.; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Apr. 26; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1942 July 3; 2p.
    - Nicholas Michelson -- from M.H. Drucker, 1931 Apr. 29
    - Nicholas Michelson -- to Lewis, J., 1938 Jan. 26; 2p
    - Nicholas Michelson -- from L.I. Dublin, 1930 Oct. 15
  - Michelson, Truman (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1910 Aug. 12
    - From Boas, 1912 Oct. 24
    - From Boas, 1912 Nov. 7
    - From Boas, 1913 Jan. 20
    - From Boas, 1913 Feb. 28
    - From Boas, 1913 Oct. 10
    - From Boas, 1913 Dec. 23
    - From Boas, 1915 Jan. 16
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 2
    - From Boas, 1917 Mar. 9
    - From Boas, 1917 Apr. 9
    - From Boas, 1917 Aug. 9; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1919 May 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 July 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 13; 1p.
    - (see Boas, F. to Tyler, J.M. Nov. 13, 1919), 1919 Nov. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Apr. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Apr. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1921 Dec. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1923 Mar. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Jan. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Feb. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1924 Oct. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 May 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 July 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Oct. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 June 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Mar. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Apr. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Sept. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Sept. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Sept. 29; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Sept. 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Oct. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 May 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 June 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 June 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 June 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 May 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Mar. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Sept. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Feb. 1; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 May 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 May 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 May 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 June 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 June 30; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Oct. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 June 9; 1p
    - To Boas, 1910 June 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1910 June 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 7; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1910 Aug. 17
    - To Boas, 1910 Sept. 1
    - To Boas, 1910 Sept. 26
    - To Boas, 1910 Oct. 13; 2p
    - To Boas, 1912 Jan. 3
    - To Boas, 1912 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 11; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Apr. 22
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 10; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 24; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Aug. 31
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 19; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Oct. 27
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 4
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 12; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 15; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Nov. 21; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 4
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 10; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Jan. 17
    - To Boas (card), 1913 Jan. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Feb. 26; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 1
    - To Boas, 1913 May 17; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1913 July 27; 7p.
    - To Boas, 1913 Aug. 20
    - To Boas, 1913 Oct. 6
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 3
    - To Boas, 1913 Nov. 29
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 12
    - To Boas, 1913 Dec. 20; 2p
    - To Boas, 1914 Dec. 16
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 8
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 16
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 24
    - To Boas, 1915 Nov. 29
    - To Boas, 1916 July 9; 4p.
    - To Boas, 1916 Aug. 11
    - To Boas, 1916 Sept. 30
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 4; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 5
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 26
    - To Boas, 1917 Apr. 28
    - To Boas, 1917 June 15; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 July 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Aug. 3; 5p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Aug. 13; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Aug. 31
    - To Boas, 1919 June 12; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Apr. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Mar. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Nov. 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1921 Dec. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1923 May 9; 1p.
    - To Boas (card), 1924 Jan. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Jan. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Feb. 25; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Oct. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 15; 1p.
    - Minutes of the organizational meeting of Linguistic Society of America.
    - (Enc. with Kent, R. G.), 1925 Jan. 12
    - To Boas, 1926 June 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 July 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Aug. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Apr. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 May 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Aug. 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Oct. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 20; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Apr. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 July 28; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Aug. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1929 July 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1930 June 9; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas (card), 1931 May 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 May 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 June 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Sept. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Sept. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Apr. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 June 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 June 6; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Sept. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Sept. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Sept. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Sept. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Oct. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Dec. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 May 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 June 19; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 July 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Oct. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Nov. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 May 15; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Dec. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Feb. 18; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Apr. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 June 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 June 5; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1937 June 25; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 29; 2p.
    - Truman Michelson -- to H.A. Andrews, 1912 July 21
    - Truman Michelson -- to H.A. Andrews, 1917 July 16
    - Truman Michelson -- to Wissler, C., 1924 Feb. 25; 3p.
    - Truman Michelson -- from Wissler, C., 1924 Feb. 25
  - Michline, W. H. (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 31; 1p.
      General note
      See also Mechling, W. H.
  - Michow, H. (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1885 June 9; 3p.
  - Mickle, R. A. (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1935 Nov. 17; 1p.
  - Middlebury College (Box 63)
    See Viltum, Murriel A.
  - Mikhaylitchenko, A. (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Jan. 15; 1p.
  - Milbank Memorial Fund (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 16; 1p.
      See Kingsbury, John A.
  - Milburn, W. J. (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1938 Jan. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Dec. 31; 2p.
    - (Enc: To whom it may concern from Thomas, Elmer), dated 12-18-37
  - Miles, Irene (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1938 Sept.9; 1p.
  - Miles, Walter R. (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 Dec. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 24; 1p.
  - Milgram, Grace (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1938 Dec. 27; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec. 22; 1p.
  - Milgram, Morris (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 31; 1p.
  - Mili, Gjon (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1940 Sept. 11; 1p.
  - Milkau, Prof. (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1920 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 16; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Oct. 8; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Nov. 3; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Dec. 31; 1p.
  - Miller, Charles P. (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1939 June 2; 1p.
  - Miller, Clyde R. (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1938 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 8; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Jan. 13; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Apr. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1912 Sept. 25
    - To Boas, 1913 Mar. 8
    - To Boas, 1938 Jan. 29; 1p.
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies, 1938 Jan.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 6; 1p.
    - (Enc: his statement re the Teachers Union, Jan. 5, 1939)
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas (open letter), 1939 June 30; 1p.
    - Clyde R. Miller -- from Abraham Flexner, 1939 July 10
    - Clyde R. Miller -- to H. D. Gideonse, 1941 Oct. 15; 1p.
    - Clyde R. Miller -- from Arthur Holcombe, 1939 July 9
    - Clyde R. Miller -- from Chester Lloyd Jones, 1939 July 5
    - Clyde R. Miller -- from G.N. Kefauver, 1939 July 7
    - Clyde R. Miller -- from Samuel B. Morris, 1939 July 7
    - Clyde R. Miller -- from H.B. Williams, 1939 July 7
  - Miller, Dixie (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 29; 2p.
  - Miller, Frank J. (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1920 Aug. 9; 1p.
  - Miller, F. Morris (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1937 Aug. 11; 1p.
  - Miller, F. R. H. (Box 63)
    - F. R. H. Miller -- to George Marshall, 1940 Mar. 4; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Marshall, George, Mar. 13, 1940)
  - Miller, Herbert A. (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1921 Feb. 8; 1p.
  - Miller, H. R. (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 3; 1p.
  - Miller, Julius S. (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1933 Dec. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Dec. 6; 2p.
  - Miller, Persis (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1940 July 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Aug. 3; 1p.
  - Miller, Rachel A. (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1929 Apr. 17; 1p.
  - Miller, Ralph F. (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1918 Mar. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 13; 1p.
  - Miller, Ray E. (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1931 June 22; 1p.
  - Millikan, Robert A. (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 18
    - From Boas, 1917 Oct. 30; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Oct. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1917 Oct. 29
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Oct. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Dec. 7; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 8; 1p.
  - Milliken, John B. (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 21
  - Mills, C. A. (Box 63)
    - C.A. Mills -- from Franklin H. Church, 1936 Oct. 3
    - (Enc. with Church, F.H., Oct. 10, 1936
  - Mills, Frederick C. (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1930 Apr. 22; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 Mar. 18; 1p.
  - Mills, John (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1925 June 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1925 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Feb. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Oct. 31; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 May 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 June 4; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1925 June 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 July 23; 3p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 2; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Feb. 21; 2p.
  - Mills, Louis I. (Box 63)
    - Louis Mills -- from L.I. Dublin, 1934 May 11
    - (Enc. with Hayden, P.M.: to Columbia Univ. Council for research in the social sciences, May 15, 1934)
  - Mills, Mountfort (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1925 Feb. 5; 1p.
  - Mills, M. G. (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1920 Sept. 14; 1p.
  - Mills, William C. (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1908 Oct. 22
    - From Boas, 1908 Nov. 9
    - From Boas, 1909 Dec. 15
    - To Boas, 1908 Oct. 30
  - Milne, G. L. (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1888 July 3; 1p.
  - Milner, Joseph Co. (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1937 Mar. 8; 1p.
  - Milpais, Mary (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1935 Aug. 10; 1p.
  - Milton, Huntington (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1910 Dec. 13; 2p.
  - Milwitzky, William (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1916 Oct. 25
    - To Boas, 1916 Oct. 26
  - Minch, Alden (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1914 Oct. 27
  - Mincrieff, D. Scott (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1996 Apr. 18
  - Miner, James Burt (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1903 Nov. 12; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 11; 1p.
  - Miner, J.W. (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1915 June 28
    - From Boas, 1915 June 30
    - From Boas, 1915 July 9
  - Miner, Louis M. (Box 63)
    - See Boas, F. Open letter on culture and democracy in Spain. Replies., 1938 Jan.
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 12; 1p.
  - Miner, Leroy M.S. (Box 63)
    - Leroy M.S. Miner -- to C.S. Minot, 1910 May 9
  - Miner, M. A. (Box 63)
    - M. A. Miner -- to F.W. Hodge, 1908 Dec. 9; 2p.
  - Miner, Ray W. (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1915 June 15
    - To Boas, 1915 June 19
    - To Boas, 1915 June 22
    - To Boas, 1915 June 26
    - To Boas, 1915 July 2
    - To Boas, 1915 July 27
  - Minister of Mexico (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1918 Oct. 15; 2p.
    - (see Bomillas, Y., Oct. 16, 1918)
  - Minner, Robert (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1936 Aug. 5; 1p.
  - Minnesota Hist. Soc. President (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1942 Nov. 23; 1p.
  - Minns, Ellis H. (Box 63)
    - (open letter), 1934 Sept. 25; 1p.
  - Minor (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 9
    - To Boas, 1907 Mar. 14
  - Minot, Charles S. (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1888 Apr. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1907 Mar. 12
    - From Boas, 1907 Oct. 22
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 23; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 Apr. 30; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1910 May 23
    - From Boas, 1910 May 26
    - To Boas, 1888 Apr. 7; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1888 Apr. 14; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1907 Oct. 18
    - To Boas, 1910 Apr. 29
    - To Boas, 1910 May 20
    - To Boas, 1910 May 25
  - Mira, Emilio (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1939 Nov. 28; 1p.
  - Miranda, Aurelio (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1915 Feb. 19
    - From Boas, 1915 Mar. 2
    - From Boas, 1915 Mar. 6
    - From Boas, 1915 Apr. 14
    - From Boas, 1915 Apr. 20
    - From Boas, 1915 May 14
    - From Boas, 1915 May 20
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb. 16
    - From Boas, 1916 Feb. 28
    - From Boas, 1917 May 14
    - From Boas, 1917 June 15
    - From Boas, 1919 Oct. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1915 Jan. 5
    - To Boas, 1915 Feb. 23
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 20
    - To Boas, 1915 Apr. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1915 June 13
    - To Boas, 1916 Feb. 10
    - To Boas, 1916 Feb. 22
    - To Boas, 1917 May 9
    - To Boas, 1917 June 25
    - To Boas, 1919 Oct. 22; 1p.
  - Mishkin (Box 63)
    - See Boas, F. (open letter), Feb. 5, 1940
  - Misochirosophus, Johannes (Box 63)
    - Johannes Misochirosophus -- to Nestor Ironside
    - (Enc. with Efron, David, July 5, 1938), 1913 June 12; 3p.
  - Mitam, A. (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1936 Jan. 10; 1p.
  - Mitchell, Bessie Merritt (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1934 Aug. 10; 6p.
  - Mitchell, C. Stanley (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1928 Sept. 12; 1p.
  - Mitchell, David (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1918 Jan. 24; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Apr. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1918 Jan. 28; 1p.
  - Mitchell, George Winter (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1919 July 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1919 July 14; 1p.
  - Mitchell, James A. (Box 63)
    - James A. Mitchell -- to Amer. Comm. for Democracy and Intellectual Freedom, 1941 Jan. 17; 1p.
  - Mitchell, Lucy Sprague (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1925 Nov. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Jan. 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Sept. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Nov. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1925 Dec. 31; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Jan. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Feb. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Sept. 25; 1p.
  - Mitchell, S. A. (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 7; 1p.
    - S. A. Mitchell -- to H. Gaston-Heye, 1940 Dec. 31
  - Mitchell, S. Weir (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1907 Sept. 11; 2p.
  - Mitchell, Wesley C. (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1926 May 27; 3p.
    - From Boas, 1926 Sept. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Mar. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Apr. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1927 Dec. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Mar. 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 July 14; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 30; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1928 Dec. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Jan. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Feb. 21; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 May 27; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1938 June 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - (see Boas, F. to Rautenstrauch, W., Dec. 22, 1941)
    - To Boas, 1926 May 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1926 Sept. 29; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1927 Dec. 23; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - (Enc: Mitchell, W.C. to Kellogg, V. Mar. 12, 1928), 1928 July 18; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 20; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1930 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Jan. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Mar. 8; 1p.
    - See Pegram, G.B. to Cabanellas, 1937 Feb. 11
    - To Boas, 1938 June 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Dec.
    - See Boas, F. (open letter), 1939 Dec.
    - To Boas, 1941 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 June 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1942 Aug. 10; 1p.
    - W.C. Mitchell -- to H. Gaston-Heye, 1940 Dec.; 1p.
    - W. C. Mitchell -- to V. Kellogg, 1928 Mar. 12; 1p.
    - W. C. Mitchell -- to E. R. Seligman, 1926 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - (Enc. with Seligman, E.R., Mar. 31, 1926)
  - Mitchell, William M. (Box 63)
    - To Boas, 1903 Sept. 10
    - To Boas, 1903 Oct. 14
    - To Boas, 1903 Nov. 27
    - To Boas, 1903 Dec. 12
    - To Boas, 1904 Mar. 1
    - To Boas, 1907 Sept. 16
  - Mixed Claims Commissions, U.S. and Mexico (Box 63)
    - From Boas, 1924 Nov. 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1924 Nov. 19; 2p.
  - Mochi, Aldobrandino
    - From Boas, 1926 Dec. 8; 1p.
  - Modern Language Association of America - Germanic Section (Box 64)
    See Heuser, F. W. J.
  - Moe, Henry Allen (Box 64)
    - 1928 Oct. 10, 2p.
    - From Boas, 1929 Dec. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1930 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Jan. 28; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Feb. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 May 18; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 June (?); 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 June (?); 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Oct. 8; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. (?); 1p.
    - From Boas, 1931 Dec. (?); 1p.
    - From Boas, 1932 Jan. 28; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Feb. 16; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1934 May 5; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 Feb. 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1935 May 15; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Jan. 9; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1936 Dec. 31; 1p.
      (Enc: Re Golomshtok, E. A., Herskovits, M.J. and F.S., Klopfer, Bruno, Lips, J.E. and Bilden, Ruediger)
    - From Boas, 1937 Mar. 15; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 June 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1937 Nov. 4; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1938 Oct. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 27; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 June 22; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 June 26; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Aug. 2; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1940 June 20; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Jan. 8; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Feb. 10; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Feb. 17; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 3; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Mar. 27; 2p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Apr. 24; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1941 Aug. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1942 Jan. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 11; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Jan. 30; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Feb. 4; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Mar. 2; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Oct. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1931 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1932 Jan. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 14; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1934 Dec. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1935 May 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1936 Dec. 16; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Jan. 15; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 5; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1937 Nov. 10; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Feb. 28; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 June 21; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1940 Nov. 26; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Feb. 13; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Apr. 9; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Apr. 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1941 Aug. 27; 1p.
    - See margin Boas,F. to Moe, H.A., 1942 Jan. 26
    - H. A. Moe -- from Duggan, S.P., 1928 Nov. 19
    - H. A. Moe -- to Fannina W. Halle, 1942 Jan. 13; 1p.
  - Moeller, Dr. (Box 64)
    - From Boas, 1920 Oct. 12; 1p.
  - Moens, Herman B. (Box 64)
    - From Boas, 1919 Nov. 25; 1p.
  - Mogchelen, P. J. van (Box 64)
    - To Boas, 1925 Apr. 3; 1p.
  - Mohr, John (Box 64)
    - From Boas, 1932 Dec. 16; 1p.
  - Mohrmann, Christine (Box 64)
    - From Boas, 1938 Mar. 11; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1939 Feb. 6; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Feb. 3; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1938 Mar. 1; 2p.
    - To Boas, 1938 May 25; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Jan. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1939 July 26; 1p.
  - Moisseiff, Leon S. (Box 64)
    - From Boas, 1928 Oct. 25; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Nov. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1928 Oct. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Nov. 17; 1p.
  - Moley, Raymond C. (Box 64)
    - From Boas, 1933 Jan. 23; 1p.
    - From Boas, 1933 Mar. 17; 1p.
    - (Enc: Boas, F. to Roosevelt, F.D., Pres. U.S., Mar. 17, 1933), 1936 Apr. 1; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Feb. 24; 1p.
    - To Boas, 1933 Mar. 24; 1p.
    - (Enc: Moley, R.C. to Ickes, H.L., Mar. 24, 1933, 1p.), 1936 Mar. 31; 1p.